<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Booster</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="menu_title">main_menu_title</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="menu_icon_title">main_menu_icon_title</string>
    <string name="booster_menu_logo_title">booster_menu_logo_title</string>
    <string name="main_menu_text">This app helps you find out what type of investor you are. Use the menu
    to access the features. This app consists of information about the Booster Kiwisaver Investment Fund and a risk questionnaire which allows you to calculate which fund suits you.</string>
    <string name="investor_types_header">Investor Types</string>
    <string name="defensive_type_title">Defensive</string>
    <string name="conservative_type_title">Conservative</string>
    <string name="balanced_type_title">Balanced</string>
    <string name="balanced_growth_title">Balanced Growth</string>
    <string name="growth_title">Growth</string>
    <string name="aggressive_growth_title">Aggressive Growth</string>
<string name="capital_guarantee_fund">The fund aims to provide relatively consistent returns, subject to a capital guarantee.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 1.5% per year above inflation over any 2-year period.
Generally, there may be small movements up and down in the value of the fund.</string>
<string name="default_saver_fund">The fund aims to provide relatively consistent but modest returns, with some capital gains over the long term.
It aims to achieve achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 2.0% per year above inflation over any 3-year period.
Generally, there will be small movements up and down in the value of the fund, reflecting its temporary holding nature.</string>
    <string name="balanced_fund">The fund aims to provide an enhanced return over the long term through capital gains.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 3% per year above inflation over any 5-year period.
There will be some movements up and down in the value of the fund.</string>
    <string name="balanced_growth_fund">The fund aims to provide long-term capital gains but to partially offset short-term movements up and down with some income assets.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 4% per year above inflation over any 7-year period.
There will be larger movements up and down in the value of the fund compared to the Balanced Fund.</string>
    <string name="high_growth_fund">The fund aims to maximise the potential for capital gains over the long term.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 5% per year above inflation over any 10-year period.
There will be significant movements up and down in the value of the fund.</string>
</resources>
