<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Booster</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="menu_title">main_menu_title</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="menu_icon_title">main_menu_icon_title</string>
    <string name="booster_menu_logo_title">booster_menu_logo_title</string>
    <string name="main_menu_text">This app helps you find out what type of investor you are. Use the menu
    to access the features. This app consists of information about the Booster Kiwisaver Investment Fund and a risk questionnaire which allows you to calculate which fund suits you.</string>
    <string name="investor_types_header">Investor Types</string>
    <string name="defensive_type_title">Defensive</string>
    <string name="conservative_type_title">Conservative</string>
    <string name="balanced_type_title">Balanced</string>
    <string name="balanced_growth_title">Balanced Growth</string>
    <string name="growth_title">Growth</string>
    <string name="aggressive_growth_title">Aggressive Growth</string>
    <string name="submit_title">Submit</string>
<string name="capital_guarantee_fund">The fund aims to provide relatively consistent returns, subject to a capital guarantee.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 1.5% per year above inflation over any 2-year period.
Generally, there may be small movements up and down in the value of the fund.</string>
<string name="default_saver_fund">The fund aims to provide relatively consistent but modest returns, with some capital gains over the long term.
It aims to achieve achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 2.0% per year above inflation over any 3-year period.
Generally, there will be small movements up and down in the value of the fund, reflecting its temporary holding nature.</string>
    <string name="balanced_fund">The fund aims to provide an enhanced return over the long term through capital gains.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 3% per year above inflation over any 5-year period.
There will be some movements up and down in the value of the fund.</string>
    <string name="balanced_growth_fund">The fund aims to provide long-term capital gains but to partially offset short-term movements up and down with some income assets.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 4% per year above inflation over any 7-year period.
There will be larger movements up and down in the value of the fund compared to the Balanced Fund.</string>
    <string name="high_growth_fund">The fund aims to maximise the potential for capital gains over the long term.
It aims to achieve returns – after fees but before tax – of at least 5% per year above inflation over any 10-year period.
There will be significant movements up and down in the value of the fund.</string>
    <string name="question_one">When do you plan to make a signiicant lump sum withdrawal from your portfolio, for example, for the purchase of a irst home
or for retirement needs? (From age 65 at the earliest)</string>
    <string name="question_one_answer_one">Within 2 years – you need a DEFENSIVE TYPE fund</string>
    <string name="question_one_answer_two">In 2 to 5 years – you need a CONSERVATIVE TYPE fund </string>
    <string name="question_one_answer_three">In 6 to 10 years – continue to next question</string>
    <string name="question_one_answer_four">In 11 to 20 years – continue to next question </string>
    <string name="question_one_answer_five">More than 20 years – continue to next question</string>


    <string name="question_two">Which of the following questions best describes your thoughts about risks and returns?</string>
    <string name="question_two_answer_one">I want to minimise my risk and am therefore willing to
accept low returns</string>
    <string name="question_two_answer_two">I am willing to take a moderate amount of risk to
generate low to medium returns</string>
    <string name="question_two_answer_three">I am willing to take a reasonable amount of risk to
provide a more medium return </string>
    <string name="question_two_answer_four">In order to receive higher returns, I am willing to take a
relatively high amount of risk</string>
    <string name="question_two_answer_five">I want to maximise my returns and am willing to accept a
high level of risk</string>

    <string name="question_three">Protecting my investment portfolio from a fall in value at any time is more important to me than achieving high returns?</string>
    <string name="question_three_answer_one">Strongly Agree</string>
    <string name="question_three_answer_two">Agree</string>
    <string name="question_three_answer_three">Neither agree or disagree</string>
    <string name="question_three_answer_four">Disagree</string>
    <string name="question_three_answer_five">Strongly Disagree</string>

    <string name="question_four">Consider you have an investment balance of at least $20,000 or more. If after a short period of time (less than 1 year) your
balance has dropped in value, which statement relects best how you would feel about this?</string>
    <string name="question_four_answer_one">I would be unhappy with any drop in value</string>
    <string name="question_four_answer_two">I would be OK with a drop in value of no more than 5%</string>
    <string name="question_four_answer_three">I would be OK with a drop in value of no more than 10%</string>
    <string name="question_four_answer_four">I would be OK with a drop in value of up to 15%</string>
    <string name="question_four_answer_five">I would be OK with a drop in value of up to 20%</string>

    <string name="question_five">How often would you tend to worry about your investment returns?</string>
    <string name="question_five_answer_one">Daily</string>
    <string name="question_five_answer_two">Monthly</string>
    <string name="question_five_answer_three">Quarterly</string>
    <string name="question_five_answer_four">Annually</string>
    <string name="question_five_answer_five">Never or only occasionally over the longer term</string>

    <string name="total_score_pre">Your total score is:</string>

    <string name="result_defensive">You are a "defensive" investor</string>
    <string name="result_conservative">You are a "conservative" investor</string>
    <string name="result_balanced">You are a "balanced" investor</string>
    <string name="result_balanced_growth">You are a "balanced Growth" investor</string>
    <string name="result_growth">You are a "growth" investor</string>
    <string name="result_aggressive_growth">You are a "aggressive growth" investor</string>

    <string name="name_title">Name</string>
    <string name="email_title">Email</string>
    <string name="phone_title">Phone</string>
    <string name="error_no_name">Please enter a name</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">Please enter a valid email address</string>
    <string name="error_no_phone">Please enter a phone number</string>
</resources>
